Undergraduate Alumni Records, 18th Century 1748-1799: Preliminary Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
- Series 1: Alumni Files, 1748-1799; 1382 files
  - Henry, James, 1794; portion of 1 box (Box 58)
  - Henry, James, 1794; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Hiester, John Sylvanus, 1794; portion of 1 box (Box 58)
  - How, Thomas Yardley, 1794; portion of 1 box (Box 58)
  - Huger, Samuel, 1794; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Hunt, Benjamin Van Cleve, 1794; portion of 1 box (Box 58)
  - Hunt, Holloway Whitefield, 1794; portion of 1 box (Box 58)
  - Hunter, Andrew, 1794; portion of 1 box (Box 58)
  - Hutchinson, Titus, 1794; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 58)
  - Hutchison, ?, 1794; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Kar, Hugh, 1794; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Ker, Hugh, 1794; portion of 1 box (Box 58)
  - Kollock, Henry, 1794; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 58)
  - Lee, ?, 1794; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Lee, William, 1794; portion of 1 box (Box 58)
  - Lee, William L., 1794; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Leech, George W., 1794; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Leigh, Reuben, 1794; portion of 1 box (Box 58)
  - Neilson, James H., 1794; portion of 1 box (Box 58)
  - Parker, John, 1794; portion of 1 box (Box 58)
  - Paulison, Paul, 1794; portion of 1 box (Box 58)
  - Polhemus, Henry, 1794; portion of 1 box (Box 58)
  - Reese, Edwin Tasker, 1794; portion of 1 box (Box 58)
  - Robinson, ?, 1794; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Rush, John, 1794; portion of 1 box (Box 58)
  - Simpson, John Neeley, 1794; portion of 1 box (Box 59)
  - Sitler, unknown, 1794; portion of 1 box (Box 59)
  - Slemmons, John Brown, 1794; portion of 1 box (Box 59)
  - Smith, ?, 1794; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Smith, John, 1794; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Snowden, Wallace, 1794; portion of 1 box (Box 59)
  - Snowdon, ?, 1794; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Tenant, ?, 1794; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Voorhees, Samuel, 1794; portion of 1 box (Box 59)
  - Wallace, John Bradford, 1794; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 59)
  - Williamson, James Cara, 1794; portion of 1 box (Box 59)
  - Williamson, William R., 1794; portion of 1 box (Box 59)
  - Witherspoon, John Ramsay, 1794; portion of 1 box (Box 59)
  - Agnew, James, 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 59)
  - Archer, Edward, 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 59)
  - Bowie, George G., 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 59)
  - Boyd, John Adam, 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 59)
  - Brown, Thomas, 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 59)
  - Campbell, unknown, 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 59)
  - Comfort, David, 1795; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 59)
  - Condit, Silas, 1795; portion of 1 box Contains oversize material. (Box 59)
  - Cuthbert, George Ross, 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Fleming, Thomas F., 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Fleming, Thomas F., 1795; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Gibbs, ?, 1795; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Gibbs, Benjamin, 1795; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Gibbs, Benjamin, Jr., 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Harrison, Josiah, 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Hartman, Isaac, 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Hayes, Samuel, 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Herring, Elbert, 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Houstoun, Patrick, 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Keene, Richard Raynal, 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Keyes, Eleazer W., 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Lefferty, Johnson, 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Lott, ?, 1795; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Lott, Robert, 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Morgan, George, Jr., 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Morton, George Clark, 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Murch, ?, 1795; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Neely (Niely), Reuben, 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Ogden, George Montgomery, 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Parrot (Parrott), Joseph, 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Pasea, Jacob, 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Pusa, Jacob, 1795; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Riggs, Elias, 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Robertson, Isaac, 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Rumsey, ?, 1795; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Rumsey, Benjamin, 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Scott, Joseph Warren, 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Scott, Moses, 1795; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Sergeant, John, 1795; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 60)
  - Shaw, Alexander Watson, 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Simmons, ?, 1795; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Simmons, Peter, 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Smith, Edward Darrell, 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Smith, John Witherspoon, 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Smith, Owen, 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Smith, Samuel, 1795; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Snowden, William, 1795; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Starke, John Turner, 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Starks, ?, 1795; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Striker, ?, 1795; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Stryker, James S., 1795; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Stryker (Striker), James S., 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Taylor, John, 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Taylor, Robert Johnstone, 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Ten Eyck, Abraham Richard, 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Tilden, William Blay, 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Tilton, James, 1795; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 60)
  - Tilton, Thomas, 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Van Bibber, unknown, 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Van Doren, Peter Aaron, 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Wallace, Matthew Green, 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Wright, Clayton, 1795; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Anderson, William Thomas, 1796; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Axtell, Henry, Jr., 1796; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Barber, George Clinton, 1796; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Beaubien, Benjamin, 1796; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Berrien, John Macpherson, 1796; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 60)
  - Caldwell, Elias Boudinot, 1796; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Cane, ?, 1796; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Cantine, Moses I., 1796; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Crane, C., 1796; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Cunningham, unknown, 1796; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Dayton, ?, 1796; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Dayton, Elias, 1796; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Edmonds, ?, 1796; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Edmonds (Edmunds), unknown, 1796; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Edwards, John Starke, 1796; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Eltinge (Elting), Wilhelmus, 1796; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Fitzgerald, John, 1796; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Fleming, William, 1796; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Forsyth, ?, 1796; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Forsyth, Robert Marshall, 1796; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Gaston, William Joseph, 1796; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 60)
  - Guion, Isaac Lee, 1796; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Halstead, unknown, 1796; portion of 1 box (Box 60)
  - Henry, E., 1796; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - Ivers, Thomas, 1796; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - Kettle, ?, 1796; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Kettle (Kattle), William, 1796; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - Littlejohn, Joseph Blount, 1796; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - Ludlow, George Craig, 1796; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - McMullen, French F., 1796; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - Moody, John, 1796; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - Ogden, Henry W., 1796; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - Pearson, Jesse A., 1796; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - Pendleton, Philip Clayton, 1796; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - Reade, Joseph, 1796; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - Scott, George M., 1796; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - Shaw, ?, 1796; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Venable, Nathaniel E., 1796; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - Willing, ?, 1796; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Willing, William Shippen, 1796; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - Agnew, Martin, 1797; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - Agnew, William, 1797; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - Alston, Joseph, 1797; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - Bayly, Thomas, 1797; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - Beasley, Frederick, 1797; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 61)
  - Beatty, Richard Longstreet, 1797; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - Clark (Clarke), James West, 1797; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - Clay, Ralph, 1797; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - Coe, Aaron, 1797; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - Cox, ?, 1797; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Crane, Daniel, 1797; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - Crane, Israel, 1797; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - Dayton, Jonathan Horatio, 1797; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - Edwards, Henry Waggaman, 1797; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - Frazer, William Clark, 1797; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 61)
  - Hall, H.G., 1797; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - Harrison, Abraham, 1797; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - Harvey, unknown, 1797; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - Hasbrouck, Louis, 1797; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - Hughes, Thomas Edgar, 1797; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - Jackson, Robert H., 1797; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - Kerr, Alexander S., 1797; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - King, Asa, 1797; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - LeConte, Peter, 1797; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Le Conte (Chapman), Peter, 1797; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - McComb (Macomb), Thomas Irons, 1797; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - Mercer, Charles Fenton, 1797; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - Morford, Edmund, 1797; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - Otto, Jacob Schweighauser, 1797; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - Peyton, John Howe, 1797; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - Phillips, William R., 1797; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - Raven (Ravens), Lawrence L., 1797; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - Reed, Dennis DeBerdt, 1797; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - Rush, Richard, 1797; portion of 1 box (Box 61)
  - Skinner, Joseph Blount, 1797; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Stoops, John, 1797; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Strawbridge, John, 1797; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Taliaferro, Francis, 1797; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Thompson, Stephen Ogden, 1797; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Troup, George McIntosh, 1797; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 62)
  - Van Cleve, John, 1797; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Wallace, ?, 1797; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Wallace, Gustavus Brown, 1797; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Watson, John, 1797; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Cunningham, ?, 1798; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Ewing, Charles, 1798; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 62)
  - Foster, ?, 1798; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Foster, John, 1798; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Hall, H. G., 1798; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Henderson, John, 1798; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Hopkins, Benjamin Brunson, 1798; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Huger, Daniel Elliott, 1798; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Jackson, George W., 1798; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Jones, Edward Hugh, 1798; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - King, A., 1798; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Lee, Cassius, 1798; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Philips, ?, 1798; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Reed, George Washington, 1798; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Sergeant, Henry, 1798; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Sergeant, Thomas, 1798; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 62)
  - Smith, Walter T., 1798; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Smock, Cornelius, 1798; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Stockton, Thomas, 1798; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Talbot, Theodore F., 1798; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Taylor, Thomas, 1798; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Thornton, William, 1798; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Van Artsdalen, John, 1798; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - VanArtsdalen, Josh, 1798; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - VanMater, Abraham, 1798; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Van Mater, Joseph Holmes, 1798; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Watson, Josiah, 1798; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Wilson, John Curtis, 1798; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Yates, John Orfeur, 1798; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Alston, John Ashe, 1799; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Alston, William Algernon III, 1799; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Ball, Samuel, 1799; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Burnet, Eleazer, 1799; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Custis, George Washington Parke, 1799; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Early, Clement, 1799; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Forster, ?, 1799; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Forsyth, John, 1799; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 62)
  - Harris, Israel, 1799; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Horsey, ?, 1799; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Ingersoll, Charles Jared, 1799; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Jenkins, William, 1799; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Johnson, James Cathcart, 1799; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Jones, Thomas, 1799; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Ketcham, Jonathan, 1799; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Lloyd, John, 1799; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Meason, Isaac, 1799; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Meason, John, 1799; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Miller, Thomas, 1799; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Nash, Frederick, 1799; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Otto, Daniel Bodo, 1799; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Phillips, William Ralph, 1799; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Powell, Alfred Harrison, 1799; portion of 1 box Contains photographs. (Box 62)
  - Rogers, James, 1799; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Sewell, ?, 1799; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Smith, W. R., 1799; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Stewart, ?, 1799; multiple boxes (Box Non-graduate card file)
  - Stewart, William, 1799; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Van Dyke, John, 1799; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Villetard, John W., 1799; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Wisner, Henry G., 1799; portion of 1 box (Box 62)
  - Young, John Richardson, 1799; 1 box (Box 63)